Guide to the William Rose Benét Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1897-1955; 1922-1950; Series I; 22.43; 50 boxes
  - General Correspondence
    - Yaddo (Artists' Colony), 1926; 1950 (Box 47, Folder 1918)
    - The Yale Review (to Elinor Wylie), 1922; 1924 (Box 47, Folder 1919)
    - Yale Record, 1905 December 4 (Box 47, Folder 1920)
    - Yale University, 1916-1950, undated (Box 47, Folder 1921)
    - Yale University. Library, 1940–1954 (Box 47, Folder 1922)
    - Yale University Press, 1915–1950 (Box 47, Folder 1923)
    - Yarmolinsky, Avrahm, 1942 December 7 (Box 47, Folder 1924)
    - Yarros, Victor S., 1947-1948, undated (Box 47, Folder 1925)
    - Ylla, 1944–1945 (Box 47, Folder 1926)
    - Young, Ella (to Elinor Wylie), 1927–1945 (Box 47, Folder 1927)
    - Young, Esther, 1941–1944 (Box 47, Folder 1928)
    - Young, G. M. [(George Malcolm)?], undated (Box 47, Folder 1929)
    - Young, George (to Elinor Wylie), 1927-1928, undated (Box 47, Folder 1930)
    - Young, George, [Sir?], 1926-1928, undated (Box 47, Folder 1931)
    - Young, Joan (to Elinor Wylie), 1926, undated (Box 48, Folder 1932)
    - Young, J. Helen (to Elinor Wylie), 1926-1930, undated (Box 48, Folder 1933-1934)
    - Young, Stanley, 1948 January 26 (Box 48, Folder 1935)
    - "Z" general, 1929–1949 (Box 48, Folder 1936)
    - Zabriskie, George, 1949–1950 (Box 48, Folder 1937)
    - Zilles, Luke Escala, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 1938)
    - Zlotnik, Harold, 1947–1950 (Box 48, Folder 1939)
    - Zoglin, Rosalind, 1944 September 1 (Box 48, Folder 1940)
    - Unidentified, 1908-1949, undated (Box 48, Folder 1941-1942)
    - Empty envelopes, 1919-1937, undated (Box 48, Folder 1943)
  - First Name Only
    - "A", 1926-1948, undated (Box 48, Folder 1944)
    - "B", 1928-1949, undated (Box 48, Folder 1945)
    - "C", 1918-1950, undated (Box 48, Folder 1946)
    - "D", 1920-1950, undated (Box 48, Folder 1947)
    - "E", 1928-1950, undated (Box 48, Folder 1948)
    - "F", 1939; 1949 (Box 48, Folder 1949)
    - "G", 1928-1948, undated (Box 48, Folder 1950)
    - "H", 1931-1935, undated (Box 48, Folder 1951)
    - "I", 1930; 1944 (Box 48, Folder 1952)
    - "J", 1905-1906, undated (Box 48, Folder 1953)
    - "L", 1943-1950, undated (Box 48, Folder 1954)
    - "M", 1909-1947, undated (Box 48, Folder 1955-1956)
    - "N", 1942, undated (Box 48, Folder 1957)
    - "P", 1926-1934, undated (Box 48, Folder 1958)
    - "R", 1928–1949 (Box 48, Folder 1959)
    - "S", 1929-1950, undated (Box 48, Folder 1960)
    - "T", 1926-1946, undated (Box 48, Folder 1961)
    - "V", undated (Box 48, Folder 1962)
    - "W", 1905; 1945 (Box 48, Folder 1963)
  - Third Party Correspondence
    - A. M. Robertson to Duffield Green, 1934 February 19 (Box 49, Folder 1964)
    - Albert Charles Boni to Daniel T. Walden, 1934 (Box 49, Folder 1965)
    - Allen, Sara van Alstyne to Amy Loveman, 1950 May 16 (Box 49, Folder 1966)
    - Arensberg, Walter to Duffield Green, 1934 March 12 (Box 49, Folder 1967)
    - Baxter, Dorothy to various, 1949, undated (Box 49, Folder 1968)
    - Benson, Stella to Marie Welch, 1932 November 22 (Box 49, Folder 1969)
    - Blackwell, Alice Stone to Random House, 1945 (Box 49, Folder 1970)
    - Bobbs-Merrill Company to Duffield Green, 1934 February 19 (Box 49, Folder 1971)
    - Brewer, Joseph to Irving Ruland Company, Inc., 1929 (Box 49, Folder 1972)
    - Brockway, Howard to Mr. James, 1947 April 24 (Box 49, Folder 1973)
    - Brown, Hilton to Mr. Berril, 1949 February 17 (Box 49, Folder 1974)
    - Carruth, Gorton to Helen Power, 1955 December 21 (Box 49, Folder 1975)
    - Charles Scribner's Sons to Duffield & Green, 1934 (Box 49, Folder 1976)
    - Clegg, Sarah to E. L. Roberts, 1937 July 16 (Box 49, Folder 1977)
    - Coward-McCann Inc. to Duffield Green, 1934 (Box 49, Folder 1978)
    - D. Appleton and Company to Duffield Green, 1934 February 16 (Box 49, Folder 1979)
    - Daly's Theatre (London, England) to Mrs. Herbert, 1897 January 2 (Box 49, Folder 1980)
    - David Robbins Productions to Harold Ober Associates, 1948 June 7 (Box 49, Folder 1981)
    - Dawson, Mitchell to The Nation, 1944 December 1 (Box 49, Folder 1982)
    - Denny, Thomas Gwinn to Saturday Review of Literature, 1953 January 26 (Box 49, Folder 1983)
    - Dial Press to Duffield Green, 1934 February 21 (Box 49, Folder 1984)
    - Doubleday, Doran and Company to Captain S.G.S. McNeil, 1928 December 17 (Box 49, Folder 1985)
    - Eden, Pauline to Duffield Green, 1934 February 28 (Box 49, Folder 1986)
    - Famous Players-Lasky Corporation to Loila Brooks, 1922 May 18 (Box 49, Folder 1987)
    - Farrar Rinehart to Duffield Green, 1934 February 17 (Box 49, Folder 1988)
    - George H. Brennan to Miss Brooks, 1921 February 5 (Box 49, Folder 1989)
    - John Day Company to Duffield Green, 1934 (Box 49, Folder 1990)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation to William Lyon Phelps, 1925 December 14 (Box 49, Folder 1991)
    - Lindsay, Elisabeth Conner to Mr. Harris, undated (Box 49, Folder 1992)
    - Liveright Publishing Corporation to Duffield Green, 1934 (Box 49, Folder 1993)
    - The London Mercury to Mrs. Mordaunt, 1928 June 18 (Box 49, Folder 1994)
    - Luce, Robert to Time, 1924 July (Box 49, Folder 1995)
    - Moore, Marianne to Duffield Green, 1934 February 23 (Box 49, Folder 1996)
    - Nock, S[amuel] A[lbert] to Mr. Stevens, 1934 October 19 (Box 49, Folder 1997)
    - O'Brian, John Lord to M. A. DeWolfe Howe, 1950 January 5 (Box 49, Folder 1998)
    - Robert M. McBride Company to Duffield Green, 1934 February 19 (Box 49, Folder 1999)
    - Rodd, [Rennell?] to "George", 1927 March 20 (Box 49, Folder 2000)
    - Saturday Review of Literature to Yale University Library, 1950 July 25 (Box 49, Folder 2001)
    - Shelley, Percy Bysshe to unidentified, undated
    - Smith, Francie Hopkinson to J. H. K. Shannahan, 1915 February 26 (Box 49, Folder 2002)
    - Street, Helen E. to Mr. McBlair, 1929 February 19 (Box 49, Folder 2003)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell Company to Rinehart Company, 1955 December 21 (Box 49, Folder 2004)
    - Tomasulo, Angelo J. to National Institute of Arts and Letters (U.S.), 1947 May 7 (Box 49, Folder 2005)
    - United States. Attorney-General to National Institute of Arts and Letters (U.S.), 1944 March 25 (Box 49, Folder 2006)
    - Van Doren, Mark to Miss Mulcahy, 1950 July 1 (Box 49, Folder 2007)
    - Viking Press Inc. to Duffield Green, 1934 February 26 (Box 49, Folder 2008)
    - Vintner, Robert D. to Dr. Moore, undated (Box 49, Folder 2009)
    - Walters, Raymond to David McCord, 1950 January 5 (Box 49, Folder 2010)
    - Warnock, Robert to Mr. Canby, 1932 August 19 (Box 49, Folder 2011)
    - Yeats, W. B. (William Butler) to E. C. Yeats, [1924?] (Box 49, Folder 2012)
    - "Guillaume" to unidentified, undated (Box 49, Folder 2013)
    - Unidentified to Edgar W. Smith, 1942 August 5 (Box 49, Folder 2014)
    - Unidentified to Kenelm Digby, 1923 April 9 (Box 49, Folder 2015)
    - Unidentified to Public Ledger, 1928 March 30 (Box 49, Folder 2016)
    - Unidentified to "Auree", 1907 June 3 (Box 49, Folder 2017)
    - Various to B. Brooks, 1922 November 9 (Box 49, Folder 2018)
- Family Correspondence, 1883-1956; Series II; 9.17; 22 boxes
  Organized into two subseries: General Correspondence and Other Family Letters. General Correspondence is arranged alphabetically first by correspondent (sender) and then by recipient. Letters are arranged chonologically within files. Other Family Letters are arranged alphabetically.
  Series II. Family Correspondence consists chiefly of letters between members of the Benét and Rose families. Large files can be found: between William Rose Benét and his mother, Frances Rose Benét, his father, James Walker Benét, and his sister, Laura Benét; to William Rose Benét from his three children, James Benét, Frances Rosemary (Benét) Dawson, and Kathleen Anne (Benét) Fry; and from William Rose Benét to his maternal grandmother, M. L. Rose, and his spouses, Teresa Frances (Thomson) Benét and Elinor Wylie.
  Letters to and from in-laws can also be found here. There are letters with Kathleen and Charles Gilman Norris, for example, in-laws through Benét's marriage to Teresa Frances Thomson, and with members of the Hoyt family, in-laws through Benét's marriage to Elinor Wylie. In additon, there are third-party letters from non-family members.
  - General Correspondence
    - Baxter, Dorothy
      - Benét, William Rose, 1928–1949 (Box 50, Folder 2019)
    - Baxter, Lora (spouse)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 2020)
      - Benét, Laura, 1934, undated (Box 50, Folder 2021)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1932-1950, undated (Box 50, Folder 2022-2034)
      - Benét, William Rose, undated (Box 51, Folder 2035)
    - Beal, Telka (niece)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1950, undated (Box 51, Folder 2036)
    - Beal, William R. (nephew)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1945–1946 (Box 51, Folder 2037)
    - Benét, Carmen
      - Unidentified, 1940 December 12 (Box 51, Folder 2038)
    - Benét, Frances Rose (mother)
      - Benét, James, 1914-, 1924, undated (Box 51, Folder 2039)
      - Benét, James Walker, 1897 August (Box 51, Folder 2040)
      - Benét, Teresa Frances (Thomson), undated (Box 51, Folder 2041)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1898–1906 (Box 51, Folder 2042-2052)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1907–1933 (Box 52, Folder 2053-2065)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1933-1940, undated (Box 53, Folder 2066-2081)
      - Benét, William Rose, undated (Box 54, Folder 2082-2089)
      - [Benét?] "children", 1932 December 20 (Box 54, Folder 2090)
      - [Dawson, Frances Rosemary (Benét)?], 1923, undated (Box 54, Folder 2091)
      - Fry, Kathleen Anne (Benét), undated (Box 54, Folder 2092)
      - Rose, M. L., 1906 December 27 (Box 54, Folder 2093)
      - Wylie, Elinor, 1923 March 4 (Box 54, Folder 2094)
      - "Mollie", 1906 April 27 (Box 54, Folder 2095)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 54, Folder 2096)
    - Benét, James, 1914- (son)
      - Baxter, Lora, 1933; 1934 (Box 54, Folder 2097)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1938 July 16 (Box 54, Folder 2098)
      - Benét, Frances Rose; Benét, James Walker, undated (Box 54, Folder 2099)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1920–1944 (Box 54, Folder 2100-2105)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1944-1950, undated (Box 55, Folder 2106-2110)
      - Bliven, Bruce, 1937 April 24 (Box 55, Folder 2111)
      - Flack, Marjorie, 1944–1950 (Box 55, Folder 2112)
      - Norris, Charles Gilman, 1928, undated (Box 55, Folder 2113)
      - Thomson, Frederick, 1938 May 15 (Box 55, Folder 2114)
      - Wylie, Elinor, 1924, undated (Box 55, Folder 2115)
    - Benét, James Walker (father)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1905, undated (Box 55, Folder 2116)
      - Benét, Laura, 1904 December 10 (Box 55, Folder 2117)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1904–1909 (Box 55, Folder 2118-2126)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1909-1928, undated (Box 56, Folder 2127-2129)
      - Dawson, Frances Rosemary (Benét), [?] November 10 (Box 56, Folder 2130)
      - Rose, M. L., 1883 (Box 56, Folder 2131)
      - Wylie, Elinor, undated (Box 56, Folder 2132)
    - Benét, Laura (sister)
      - Baxter, Lora, 1933, undated (Box 56, Folder 2133)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, undated (Box 56, Folder 2134)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1920 October 7 (Box 56, Folder 2135)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1906–1950 (Box 56, Folder 2136-2146)
      - Benét, William Rose, undated (Box 57, Folder 2147-2151)
      - Benét, William Rose; Baxter, Lora, 1932-1933, undated (Box 57, Folder 2152)
      - Benét, William Rose; Flack, Marjorie, 1941-1949, undated (Box 57, Folder 2153-2154)
      - Dawson, Frances Rosemary (Benét), 1923 November 29 (Box 57, Folder 2155)
      - Flack, Marjorie, 1942-1949, undated (Box 57, Folder 2156-2157)
      - Unidentified, 1942, undated (Box 57, Folder 2158)
    - Benét, Laurence Vincent (uncle)
      - Benét, Laura, 1946–1947 (Box 57, Folder 2159)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1904-1947, undated (Box 57, Folder 2160-2161)
    - Benét, Margaret Cox
      - Benét, James Walker, 1906–1908 (Box 57, Folder 2162)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1940 December 24 (Box 57, Folder 2163)
    - Benét, Mary
      - Benét, William Rose, 1940–1949 (Box 57, Folder 2164)
      - Benét, William Rose; Flack, Marjorie, 1941-1950, undated (Box 57, Folder 2165)
    - Benét, Rachel (niece)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1944-1946, undated (Box 57, Folder 2166)
      - Benét, William Rose; Flack, Marjorie, 1945-1949, undated (Box 58, Folder 2167)
    - Benét, Rosemary (sister-in-law)
      - Barnum, Hilma, undated (Box 58, Folder 2168)
      - Benét, William Rose, undated (Box 58, Folder 2169)
      - Benét, William Rose; Flack, Marjorie, undated (Box 58, Folder 2170)
      - Flack, Marjorie, undated (Box 58, Folder 2171)
      - Wylie, Elinor, 1928, undated (Box 58, Folder 2172)
      - Unidentified, 1923-1945, undated (Box 58, Folder 2173)
    - Benét, S. V. (Stephen Vincent) (grandfather)
      - Benét, James Walker, 1891-1892, undated (Box 58, Folder 2174)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1886 February 3 (Box 58, Folder 2175)
      - Ellis, W. J. F., 1890 October 15 (Box 58, Folder 2176)
    - Benét, Stephanie
      - Benét, William Rose, 1935, undated (Box 58, Folder 2177)
      - Benét, William Rose; Flack, Marjorie, 1948–1949 (Box 58, Folder 2178)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 58, Folder 2179)
    - Benét, Stephen Vincent (brother)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, undated (Box 58, Folder 2180)
      - Benét, Teresa Frances (Thomson), 1912 February 13 (Box 58, Folder 2181)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1904-1942, undated (Box 58, Folder 2182-2186)
      - Rose, M. L., undated (Box 58, Folder 2187)
      - Wylie, Elinor, undated (Box 58, Folder 2188)
    - Benét, Teresa Frances (Thomson) (spouse)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1918, undated (Box 58, Folder 2189)
      - Benét, William Rose, undated (Box 58, Folder 2190)
    - Benét, Thomas C. (nephew)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1948-1949, undated (Box 58, Folder 2191)
      - Benét, William Rose; Flack, Marjorie, 1944-1950, undated (Box 58, Folder 2192)
      - Flack, Marjorie, 1950 May 5 (Box 58, Folder 2193)
    - Benét, William Rose
      - Baxter, Lora, 1934–1950 (Box 58, Folder 2194)
      - Beal, Telka (niece), 1949 February 17 (Box 58, Folder 2195)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1898–1905 (Box 58, Folder 2196-2198)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1905–1916 (Box 59, Folder 2199-2212)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1916–1935 (Box 60, Folder 2213-2225)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1935–1939 (Box 61, Folder 2226-2238)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, undated (Box 62, Folder 2239-2241)
      - Benét, Frances Rose; Benét, James Walker, 1905-1928, undated (Box 62, Folder 2242-2243)
      - Benét, Frances Rose; Benét, Laura, 1930-1939, undated (Box 62, Folder 2244-2248)
      - Benét, James, 1914-, 1917-1950, undated (Box 62, Folder 2249)
      - Benét, James Walker, 1897–1906 (Box 62, Folder 2250-2253)
      - Benét, James Walker, 1906-1927, undated (Box 63, Folder 2254-2262)
      - Benét, Kathleen Anne, undated (Box 63, Folder 2263)
      - Benét, Laura, 1903–1946 (Box 63, Folder 2264-2267)
      - Benét, Laura, 1946-1950, undated (Box 64, Folder 2268-2269)
      - Benét, Laurence Vincent, 1946 December 11 (Box 64, Folder 2270)
      - Benét, [Mary?], 1947 June 27 (Box 64, Folder 2271)
      - Benét, Rachel, 1944-1946, undated (Box 64, Folder 2272)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1946–1950 (Box 64, Folder 2273)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1904-1920, undated (Box 64, Folder 2274)
      - Benét, Teresa Frances (Thomson), 1917–1918 (Box 64, Folder 2275-2284)
      - Benét, Teresa Frances (Thomson), 1928, undated (Box 65, Folder 2285-2287)
      - Benét, Thomas, 1948–1950 (Box 65, Folder 2288)
      - Carr, Rachel H., 1929, undated (Box 65, Folder 2289)
      - Dawson, Frances Rosemary (Benét), 1918–1950 (Box 65, Folder 2290)
      - Flack, Marjorie, 1938-1944, undated (Box 65, Folder 2291-2293)
      - Flack, Miriam, 1949 Janaury 12 (Box 65, Folder 2294)
      - Fry, Kathleen Anne (Benét), 1946–1950 (Box 65, Folder 2295)
      - Hichborn, Philip, 1929 (Box 65, Folder 2296)
      - Mahon, Agnes, 1912–1917 (Box 65, Folder 2297)
      - Norris, Charles Gilman, 1929 (Box 65, Folder 2298)
      - Norris, Kathleen, 1917-1950, undated (Box 65, Folder 2299)
      - Parrish, Kathie, 1947 January 3 (Box 65, Folder 2300)
      - [Rose, Elizabeth Neill?], 1898 (Box 65, Folder 2301)
      - Rose, M. L., 1892–1911 (Box 65, Folder 2302-2305)
      - Rose, M. L., 1912-1917, undated (Box 66, Folder 2306-2308)
      - Rose, M. L.; Rose, Elizabeth Neill, 1897–1913 (Box 66, Folder 2309-2310)
      - Thompson, Joseph S., 1947 January 3 (Box 66, Folder 2311)
      - Wylie, Elinor, 1920–1926 (Box 66, Folder 2312-2321)
      - Wylie, Elinor, 1926-1928, undated (Box 67, Folder 2322-2331)
      - Unidentified, 1897-[1920s], undated (Box 67, Folder 2332)
      - Empty folder, undated (Box 67, Folder 2333)
    - Dawson, Richard S.
      - Benét, William Rose, [?] August 31 (Box 67, Folder 2334)
      - Benét, William Rose; Flack, Marjorie, 1944 July 2 (Box 67, Folder 2335)
    - Dawson, Frances Rosemary (Benét) (daughter)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1930-1931, undated (Box 67, Folder 2336)
      - Benét, Frances Rose; Benét, Laura, undated (Box 67, Folder 2337)
      - Benét, Laura, undated (Box 67, Folder 2338)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1923-1947, undated (Box 67, Folder 2339-2342)
      - Benét, William Rose; Baxter, Lora, 1933, undated (Box 68, Folder 2343)
      - Benét, William Rose; Flack, Marjorie, 1947, undated (Box 68, Folder 2344-2346)
      - Benét, William Rose; Wylie, Elinor, 1925-1927, undated (Box 68, Folder 2347)
      - Flack, Marjorie, 1950 May (Box 68, Folder 2348)
      - Norris, Charles Gilman; Norris, Kathleen, 1925 October (Box 68, Folder 2349)
      - Wylie, Elinor, undated (Box 68, Folder 2350)
      - "Family", 1933, undated (Box 68, Folder 2351)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 68, Folder 2352)
    - Flack, Bob
      - Benét, William Rose, 1944–1945 (Box 68, Folder 2353)
    - Flack, John Brooks
      - Benét, William Rose, 1943 April 12 (Box 68, Folder 2354)
      - Flack, Marjorie, 1943-1950, undated (Box 68, Folder 2355)
    - Flack, Marjorie
      - Benét, James, 1914-, 1950, undated (Box 68, Folder 2356)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1936-1945, undated (Box 68, Folder 2357-2359)
      - Printed card removed from Benét, William Rose, undated (Box 114 (Oversize), Folder 3335)
      - Unidentified, 1954, undated (Box 68, Folder 2360)
    - Flack, Miriam
      - Flack, Marjorie, undated (Box 68, Folder 2361)
    - Fry, George Blanchard
      - Benét, William Rose, 1943; 1949 (Box 68, Folder 2362)
    - Fry, Kathleen Anne (Benét)
      - Baxter, Lora, 1933–1934 (Box 68, Folder 2363)
      - Benét, Frances Rose; Benét, Laura, undated (Box 68, Folder 2364)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1924-1946, undated (Box 68, Folder 2365-2370)
      - Benét, William Rose; Baxter, Lora, 1932-1935, undated (Box 68, Folder 2371)
      - Benét, William Rose; Benét, Teresa Frances (Thomson), 1927 (Box 68, Folder 2372)
      - Benét, William Rose; Flack, Marjorie, 1943-1949, undated (Box 69, Folder 2373-2374)
      - Benét, William Rose; Wylie, Elinor, 1928, undated (Box 69, Folder 2375)
      - Flack, Marjorie, 1941-1950, undated (Box 69, Folder 2376)
      - Norris, Kathleen, 1925 October 24 (Box 69, Folder 2377)
      - Wylie, Elinor, undated (Box 69, Folder 2378)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 69, Folder 2379)
    - Hartigan, Charles Conway
      - Benét, Laura, 1909 May 21 (Box 69, Folder 2380)
    - Hichborn, Philip
      - Benét, William Rose, 1929, undated (Box 69, Folder 2381)
    - Hoyt, Anne
      - Benét, William Rose, 1922-1933, undated (Box 69, Folder 2382)
      - Wylie, Elinor, 1924-1928, undated (Box 69, Folder 2383)
    - Hoyt, Helen
      - Benét, William Rose, undated (Box 69, Folder 2384)
    - Hoyt, Henry Martyn
      - Benét, William Rose, 1907-1917, undated (Box 69, Folder 2385-2394)
      - Benét, William Rose, undated (Box 70, Folder 2395-2400)
      - Benét, William Rose, undated (Box 114 (Oversize), Folder 3336)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1908-1910, undated (Box 70, Folder 2401)
      - Thompson, [Teresa?], [?] April 17 (Box 70, Folder 2402)
    - Hoyt, Maud Buckingham
      - Benét, William Rose, undated (Box 70, Folder 2403)
    - Hoyt, Nancy
      - Benét, William Rose, 1934, undated (Box 70, Folder 2404)
      - Wylie, Elinor, 1926, undated (Box 70, Folder 2405)
    - Mahon, Agnes (aunt)
      - Benét, James Walker, 1925 January 8 (Box 70, Folder 2406)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1904-1927, undated (Box 70, Folder 2407)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 70, Folder 2408)
    - Mahon, John
      - Wylie, Elinor, 1923 December 12 (Box 70, Folder 2409)
    - Mahon, John M.
      - Benét, William Rose, undated (Box 70, Folder 2410)
    - Mahon, [?]
      - Unidentified, 1909 February 1 (Box 70, Folder 2411)
    - Maxwell, Anne S.
      - Benét, William Rose, [?] April 5 (Box 70, Folder 2412)
    - Norris, Charles Gilman
      - Benét, William Rose, 1909-1943, undated (Box 70, Folder 2413-2414)
    - Norris, Frank
      - Benét, William Rose, 1932-1946, undated (Box 70, Folder 2415)
    - Norris, Kathleen
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1909, undated (Box 70, Folder 2416)
      - Benét, James Walker, undated (Box 70, Folder 2417)
      - Benét, Laura, undated (Box 70, Folder 2418)
      - Benét, Teresa Frances (Thompson), undated (Box 70, Folder 2419)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1909-1946, undated (Box 70, Folder 2420-2421)
      - Benét, William Rose; Baxter, Lora, undated (Box 70, Folder 2422)
      - Benét, William Rose; Flack, Marjorie, 1949 (Box 70, Folder 2423)
      - Benét, William Rose; Wylie, Elinor, undated (Box 70, Folder 2424)
      - Flack, Marjorie, 1949-1950, undated (Box 70, Folder 2425)
      - Wylie, Elinor, 1923, undated (Box 70, Folder 2426)
      - "Mother", undated (Box 70, Folder 2427)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 70, Folder 2428)
    - [Noyes, C. Reinold (Charles Reinold)?]
      - Hoyt, Elinor, 1906 October 22 (Box 70, Folder 2429)
    - Parrish, Kathie (Thompson) (niece)
      - Benét, William Rose; Flack, Marjorie, 1943 (Box 70, Folder 2430)
      - Flack, Marjorie, 1950 May 6 (Box 70, Folder 2431)
    - Rose, Elizabeth Neil
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1905 October 23 (Box 70, Folder 2432)
    - Rose, M. L.
      - Benét, William Rose, 1904–1909 (Box 70, Folder 2433)
    - Rose, William John
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1906 October 21 (Box 70, Folder 2434)
      - Rose, M. L., 1910 August 28 (Box 70, Folder 2435)
    - Thompson, Helen Meigs
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1938 August 21 (Box 70, Folder 2436)
    - Thompson, Joseph A.
      - Benét, William Rose, 1942-1953, undated (Box 70, Folder 2437)
    - Thompson, Joseph S.
      - Benét, William Rose, 1942; 1950 (Box 70, Folder 2438)
    - First name only
      - Various, 1908-1945, undated (Box 71, Folder 2439)
    - Unidentified
      - Various, 1895, undated (Box 71, Folder 2440)
  - Other Family Letters
    - Beaume, Jeanne to Lora Baxter, 1947 September 6 (Box 71, Folder 2441)
    - Beebe, [Emily?] to Laura Benét, 1944 October 19 (Box 71, Folder 2442)
    - Benaywitz, Morris J. to James Walker Benét, 1915 October 11 (Box 71, Folder 2443)
    - [Bennett?], W. to Frances Rose Benét, 1935 February 5 (Box 71, Folder 2444)
    - Briggs, Leroy H. to Charles Gilman Norris, 1926 June 14 (Box 71, Folder 2445)
    - Brubaker, David H., Mrs. to "Mrs." Rose, 1925 January 8 (Box 71, Folder 2446)
    - Calvert School to Laura Benét, 1907 September 27 (Box 71, Folder 2447)
    - Cathedral School of St. Mary to Laura Benét, 1942 November 3 (Box 71, Folder 2448)
    - Choate School to Charles Gilman Norris, undated (Box 71, Folder 2449)
    - Clifton, Elsie to Frances Rose Benét, undated (Box 71, Folder 2450)